[
    [
        "Anthony Pearce",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Anthony Pearce",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Managing Partner",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "0467 600 061",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "anthony@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    32,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Grace Ball",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Grace Ball",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Livestock Production Specialist / Store Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    47,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "0467 600 623",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "grace@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    30,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Steve Noble",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Steve Noble",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Production Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "08 891 4629",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "office@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew Wilson",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew Wilson",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Livestock Production Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "0439 354 228",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "andrew@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tanya Hosking",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tanya Hosking",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "08 8391 4629",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "tanya@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    30,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "08 8391 4629 ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "08 8391 4629",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "office@hillsfarmsupplies.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "81 377 115 480",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "© Copyright 2018 | All Rights Reserved | Hills Farm Supplies | Designed by ACM",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    41,
                    60,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "TEL: +61 (02) 9832 2015",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    5,
                    23,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "info@tankvision.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ben Leggott - Tank Vision's Founder & Managing Director",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    55,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    28,
                    35,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    25,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "BEN LEGGOTT",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Founder & Managing Director",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    10,
                    27,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew Knox - Tank Vision's Operations Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    28,
                    46,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    25,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ANDREW KNOX",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Operations Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Farshad - Tank Vision's Design Engineer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    21,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    39,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Design Engineer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "IAN MCGREGOR",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Business Development Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Claire Multani - Tank Vision's Sales and Operations Administrator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    31,
                    65,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    28,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CLAIRE MULTANI",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sales and Operations Administrator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    34,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Daryl - Tank Vision's Installation Supervisor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    8,
                    19,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    45,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "DARYL",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Installation Supervisor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Owen - Tank Vision's Installation Supervisor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    7,
                    18,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    44,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "OWEN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Installation Supervisor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bernie - Tank Vision's Fabrication Supervisor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    9,
                    20,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    23,
                    45,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "BERNIE",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tank Vision offer the following services:",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Phone: +61 (02) 9832 2015",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    25,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: info@tankvision.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    29,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Copyright © 2019 Tank Vision. All rights reserved.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    28,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " 61 8 9274 1277  info@australiantraining.com.au   LOGIN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    15,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    47,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ALAN GREGORY",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Managing Director",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alan has almost 30 years’ experience in the aviation",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alan has successfully project managed $20M+ contracts on behalf of international clients and foreign Governments",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Responsible for all business activities and product development at Australian Training Management Pty Ltd",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    67,
                    105,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "MITCHELL BENTLEY",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "I.T Administrator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mitchell joined the company in 2011 under a Certificate III in Information Technology Traineeship.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mitchell now manages all infrastructure and IT within the business. Assisting in the development of our highly acclaimed mobile e-assessment tool",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HANNAH SCHAUB",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Training Administrator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Hannah has been part of the Australian Training Management team since 2015",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    28,
                    58,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "KRISTEN FARMER",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Client Relations",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kristen was previously engaged as Australian Training Management's Training Coordinator and in using her significant knowledge of local industry and project management",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    64,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kristen has worked in the construction industry for several years",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kristen has worked at national level for seven years and then as WA State Manager for Brauer for nineteen years",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "AARON LEAFE",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Aaron has almost 20 years first hand industry experience in the mining",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Aaron has vast expertise in and is responsible for client training needs analysis",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "PETER BURSEY",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Peter has 25+ years relevant and recent industry experience in the High Risk Work",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Engaged by Worksafe WA to provide industry insight",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    22,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "GEORGE DRAGOVIC",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Trainer Assessor",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "George has over 40 years' of operator and supervisor experience in the civil and building construction",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "George's responsibilities include plant operator training",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "PHONE: 61 8 9274 1277",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    21,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "EMAIL: info@australiantraining.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "© Australian Training Management Pty Ltd. (RTO No. 2431). All Rights Reserved. Site design by the team at zest.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    40,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "About WACOSS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    6,
                    12,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Debra Zanella",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "PRESIDENT",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Ruah",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mark Fitzpatrick",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "VICE PRESIDENT",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Telethon Speech and Hearing Centre",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    40,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Amanda Hunt",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Uniting Care West",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    23,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ashley Reid",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Cancer Council WA",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    23,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "David Cain",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Executive Director Service Delivery and Design | Communicare",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dawn Wallam",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Yorganop",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    14,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jennifer O’Mullane",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Local Drug Action Groups Inc.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    34,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Joanne Della Bona",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Executive Director | Coolabaroo",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    31,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jonathan Smith",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | ECHO Community Services",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    29,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Juan Larranaga",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Michael Piu",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | St Patrick’s Community Support Centre Limited",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Paul McMullan",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "CEO | Outcare",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    13,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Louise Giolitto",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chief Executive Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Louise Giolitto",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "louise@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Jennie Gray",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Deputy Chief Executive Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    30,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Jennie Gray",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "jennie@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jackie Bosen",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Executive Assistant",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jackie Bosen",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "jackie@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Laurene Coller",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Communications Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Laurene Coller",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "laurene@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Steve Crotty",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Director Corporate Services",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    27,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Steve Crotty",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "steve@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Salil Koonja",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Finance Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Salil Koonja",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "finance@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Vikas Kumar Singh",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Online Technologies Coordinator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Vikas Kumar Singh",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "vikas@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bree Van Haeften",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Program Support Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bree Van Haeften",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "info@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stuart Reid",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stuart Reid",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "stuart@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chris Twomey",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chris Twomey",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "chris@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Graham Hansen",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Senior Policy Officer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Graham Hansen",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "graham@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Demelza Rogers",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Project Coordinator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Demelza Rogers",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "demelza@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Emma Hardy ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Program Support Officer Social Policy",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Emma Hardy",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "emma@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Leela James",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Coordinator Community Relief & Resilience",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Leela James",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "leela@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sarah Wright ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sarah Wright",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "sarah@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sue Nye",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sue Nye",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "sue@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Carin McCashin ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Project Officer Early Years",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Carin McCashin",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "carin@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jaime Castilla Riasco",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Project Officer - DropIN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    24,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jaime Castilla Riasco",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "jaime@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alex Hughes",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Project Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alex Hughes",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "alex@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Program Support Officer Social Policy",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Felicity Townsend",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "felicity@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Phone (08) 9420 7222 Fax (08) 9486 7966Freecall 1300 658 816Email info@wacoss.org.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    66,
                    84,
                    "EMAIL"
                ],
                [
                    6,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "© Western Australian Council of Social Service Inc 2019",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    28,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew Young",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrew has over 20 years experience in senior management roles in the Australian grains industry",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tony Smith",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tony is the founder of Plum Grove Pty Ltd and currently holds the position of Chief Operating Officer. Tony is also an executive director of Plum Grove and Plum Grove’s NSW subsidiary Agrigrain. Tony has been based in agriculture his entire life",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    23,
                    41,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    101,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    119,
                    137,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    107,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    151,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    156,
                    166,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    184,
                    193,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    195,
                    199,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Before establishing Plum Grove",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    30,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ashley Bacon",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ashley joined Plum Grove in 2007 after working for 11 years in Agricultural Research. Ashley comes from a wheat and sheep farming background in Cunderdin.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    24,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Tyson Fry",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Tyson joined Plum Grove as a graduate Grains Analyst in November 2011. Since then Tyson has made the move into Pools where he is responsible for Pools trade and execution and managing Pool models in Western Australia and South Australia. Tyson hails from Benger",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    24,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    88,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "  Tracey Vaughan",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Tracey’s family hail from Frankland where they farm mixed grain and livestock. She joins the team at Plum Grove from an equities dealer where she assisted in capital raisings and client relations. Prior to this",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    9,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    112,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Her role at Plum Grove involves track transfer management",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    23,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "  Hayley Hobbs",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Hayley joined the Plum Grove team full time in 2014 after 3 seasons of working as the harvest casual. Prior to relocating to Perth for university",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    29,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "  Flossie D'souza",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    2,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " Flossie has worked with leading multinational corporations across Australia",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Pete Rees",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Pete joined Plum Grove in June 2014 after working in grain accumulation at GrainCorp.  He spent several years in agronomy and agricultural research prior to entering grain marketing and really enjoys dealing with farmers.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    22,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    84,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Pete is responsible for our grower and consultant relations and leads the Grower Services team.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Eric Tomlinson",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A graduate chartered accountant with experience in WA agribusiness services since 1998. Eric formerly worked in public practice in both Australia and England and is a member of the Institute of Chartered Accountants in England & Wales. Eric is responsible for the day to day financial operations of the business",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    236,
                    240,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kate Rebeiro",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kate joined Plum Grove in October 2011. Kate is a Chartered Accountant who has gained experience in the industry through previous roles held within the CBH Group. Kate is a member of the Institute of Chartered Accountants in Australia.  Her role also includes Company Secretary and  Manager of Risk and Compliance.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    22,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    44,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    70,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    152,
                    161,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    187,
                    221,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    260,
                    277,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    283,
                    298,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Aaron Dolin",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Aaron joined the Plum Grove team as a graduate trader.  He is now our Risk and Compliance Officer. Previously Aaron spent several years in various industries with a focus on retail and logistics management. During this time Aaron has completed a Bachelor of Commerce and hails from the South West of WA.  ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    27,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    97,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    115,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    224,
                    229,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Moi Tjin Tjhin",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Moi Tjin joined Plum Grove in 2015; her extensive knowledge of our business comes from her previous experience working in Jakarta for a range of businesses under Salim Group",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    16,
                    26,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    162,
                    173,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Melissa Ricci",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The newest member of the Plum Grove team",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    35,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rikki Foss",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rikki comes from a mixed grain and livestock farming family in Bruce Rock.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "She has previously worked in the grain industry with Grain Pool and the CBH Group as a Regional Manager. Before taking on this role at Plum Grove",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    53,
                    63,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    81,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    103,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    135,
                    145,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Office Manager and Executive Assistant",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    38,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Shiela Gould",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Shiela joined the Plum Grove family in May 2011. Her experience",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    28,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rachel Emer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rachel joined the Plum Grove team in 2017. ",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    28,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rachel’s early career was spent in the forestry and timber industry across NSW",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    8,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ben Smith",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ben builds and maintains Plum Grove’s software and website. He's worked for a wide variety of organisations over the last fifteen years",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    3,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    25,
                    37,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Linda Lilburne",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Linda has over 30 years experience working in the Information Technology sector. During this time",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Plum Grove Pty Ltd",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ABN 61 104 516 305",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    18,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Freecall 1300 411 155",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    9,
                    21,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Phone +61 (8) 9435 1022",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    6,
                    23,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Fax +61 (8) 9435 1033",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    21,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "info@plumgrove.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stephen Atcheler",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Founder & CEO",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    10,
                    13,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Christine Atcheler",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "E: christine@real-estate-outsourcing.com",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    40,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jelana De Leon",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Operations Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Brian Labalan",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sales Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kerla Lim Abanera",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HR Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "I am a qualified Chartered Accountant here in the Phillipines. REO has given me the opportunity to increase my hands on experience.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    37,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Edmailalyn Zabala",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Accountant",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " +617 3414 3936",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    15,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stephen Atcheler",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Founder & CEO",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    10,
                    13,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Christine Atcheler",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "E: christine@real-estate-outsourcing.com",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    40,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jelana De Leon",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Operations Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Brian Labalan",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sales Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kerla Lim Abanera",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HR Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "I am a qualified Chartered Accountant here in the Phillipines. REO has given me the opportunity to increase my hands on experience.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    37,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Edmailalyn Zabala",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Accountant",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        " +617 3414 3936",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    1,
                    15,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Gemma Munro",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Co-Founder and Chief Awakening Officer - PhD Psych",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    38,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Gemma Munro",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sophie Hampel",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Co-Founder and Chief Executive Officer - M.OrgPsych Registered Psychologist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    38,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sophie Hampel is the Co-Founder and CEO of Inkling",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    31,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    39,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    50,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kelly Segat",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Head of Programs",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kelly has  held a series of senior leadership positions within global firms and her journey has seen her work most recently as part of the Global Leadership teams for innovative and leading edge organisations such as LinkedIn. As both an innovative business leader and coach",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Stan Rodski",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chief Neuroscientist - B.Ec(Stats) D.Sc(Bio)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stan Rodski is an Australian neuroscientist specialising in brain performance. He has a bachelor’s degree in psychology and a doctorate of science  in biological statistics. Dr Rodski has worked as a psychologist for over 30 years and more recently has focused on the neurosciences. Stan has helped many people",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    43,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Gemma Cunningham",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Gemma (also known as Gigi) is deeply passionate about developing others and is in her happy place when she is presenting to groups or coaching one-on-one",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    25,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Gigi really geeks out on connecting with people through building instant relationships based on trust",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Libby Morrish",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Finance Manager - GradDipCA",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Libby is a Chartered Accountant who enjoys the gentle hum of a business that is running smoothly. She enjoys working with her intelligent",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    11,
                    31,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Brylee McFarlane",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Corporate Account Manager - B.AppSc CMP",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    25,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kelly Graham-Sutton",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Program Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kelly uses her exceptional organisational skills",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Megan Down",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Event Manager - Dip Event Mgmt B.A",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Megan is passionate about creating incredible events that bring people together to share",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Katrina Cole",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Marketing and Brand Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    27,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Katrina brings a wealth of knowledge with more than 15 years experience in senior marketing roles across a range of industries. Her passionate and collaborative approach has enabled her to achieve tremendous results for brands in her career. She loves nothing more than utilising her skills and expertise to build purpose-driven brands and is passionate about developing gender diversity and more opportunities for women in the workplace.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrea Lejbik",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Office Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Andrea is lover of fun",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Georgina Gladigau",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lauren Byleveld",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Project Manager - B.A",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lauren is a creative self-starter with an enduring love of managing detail. An intuitive giver",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "With 20+ years of experience as project manager & digital designer",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    32,
                    47,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    66,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Prue Belej",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Program Manager",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Prue is our beloved Program Manager. Working closely with our clients and the rest of the program team",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    20,
                    35,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "2018 © Copyright Inkling Women Pty Ltd",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    38,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Phone: (02) 9772 0124",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    21,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Paul Burke (Partner)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    19,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0428 281 809",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: paul@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Paul worked 24 years with the Commonwealth Bank and the last 5 years as Branch Manager prior to opening the firm in 1982.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    47,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    86,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alex Felici (Partner)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    20,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0417 278 536",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: alex@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alex commenced with the firm in January 2001 and is a specialist in arranging Finance Lease and Commercial Hire Purchase for all Capital Equipment requirements.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Greg Molloy (Partner)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    20,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0413 312 279",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: greg@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Greg joined the business in July 2005 after extensive experience with Macquarie Bank.  Greg specialises in Finance Lease and Commercial Hire Purchase for all Capital Equipment requirements.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    84,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    91,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chris George (Associate)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    23,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0412 570 594",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: chris@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    38,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Chris commenced in August 2002 after more than 10 years with the Commonwealth Bank and CBFC.  Chris manages Insurance Premium Funding as well as Finance Leasing and Commercial Hire Purchase for all forms of equipment.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    82,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    91,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    99,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Noel Pratt (Associate)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    21,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0409 438 011",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: noel@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Noel commenced in August 2012 after operating as a Finance Broker in his own right for 22 years. Prior to this",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    65,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Marcus Milne (Finance & Operations Coordinator)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    46,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: marcus@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    39,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Marcus commenced working with the business in March 2015. He holds a Bachelor of Commerce (Finance & Economics) from the University of New South Wales and specialises in Asset Finance.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Joel Lovatt (Trainee Broker)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    27,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Equipment Finance Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: joel@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Joel began at MHP in February 2017. He is currently completing a Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting) at Macquarie University while working on a part-time basis.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    17,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    122,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Gary Nicholl (Mortgage Specialist)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    33,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mortgage Loan Specialist",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    24,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mobile: 0409 005 053",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    8,
                    20,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: gary@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Gary joined our firm in April 2013 as our Mortgage Specialist. He has had over 45 years experience within the Financial Services industry. During this time he has held senior positions with numerous Banks & Financial Institutions and has operated as a Self Employed Mortgage Broker since 2002.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    61,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Debra Andrews (Mortgage Administrator)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    37,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mortgage Loans Administrator",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    28,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: debra@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    38,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Debra joined the firm in February 2016 and handles Mortgage Loans Administration. She has prior mortgage experience and previously worked with ANZ Bank for various years.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    151,
                    "ORGANIZATION"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kristen Horsnell (Administration Support)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    40,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: kristen@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    40,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Kristen joined the business in 2007 having come from a career with a major Accounting firm.  Kristen looks after the Accounting for the business and also prepares finance company documentation and provides general administrative support.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    100,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jodie Smith (Administration Support)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    35,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: jodie@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    38,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Jodie joined the business in June 2014 having come from an accounting background.  Jodie previously worked for an accounting firm and has also worked within a small business completing payroll.  Jodie’s primary focus is on documents",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    88,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Nadine Standaloft (Administration Support)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    41,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: nadine@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    39,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Nadine joined the firm in March 2013 having previously come from a Finance",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Megan Yates (Administration Support)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    13,
                    35,
                    "JOB_TITLE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Email: info@mikehughespartners.com.au",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    7,
                    37,
                    "EMAIL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Megan joined the business in 2018 and has past administration experience in the legal industry. Megan assists with preparing finance company documentation",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    5,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    101,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "T: (02) 9772 0124",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    17,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "F: (02) 9772 0131",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    17,
                    "TELEPHONE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "© Copyright 2016 - Mike Hughes and Partners (South West) | Hosting by AstroWebDesign.com.au",
        {
